Finding Aid for Michigan Historical Records Survey records, 1936-1942
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Survey of County Records
  - Kalamazoo County
    - Correspondence (Reel 15)
    - Historical Material (Reel 15)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 15)
    - Maps (Reel 15)
    - Draft of Guide-Government Organization (Reel 15)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings (Reel 15)
    - Other County Records
      - Salaries of County Officers 1834-1940 (Reel 15)
      - Assessments 1839-1939 (Reel 15)
  - Kalkaska County
    - Correspondence (Reel 16)
    - Historical Material (Reel 16)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 16)
    - Maps (Reel 16)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 16)
  - Kent County
    - Correspondence (Reel 16)
    - Historical Material (Reel 16)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 16)
    - Draft of Guide-Government Organization (Reel 17)
    - Maps (Reel 17)
  - Keweenaw County
    - Correspondence (Reel 17)
    - Historical Material (Reel 17)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 17)
    - Maps (Reel 17)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 17)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 17)
  - Lake County
    - Correspondence (Reel 18)
    - Historical Material (Reel 18)
    - Maps (Reel 18)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 18)
      - County Clerk (Reel 18)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 18)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 18)
      - Probate Court (Reel 18)
      - Sheriff (Reel 18)
      - Concealed Weapon Licensing Board (Reel 18)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 18)
      - Road Commission (Reel 18)
      - Plat Board (Reel 18)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 18)
  - Lapeer County
    - Correspondence (Reel 18)
    - Historical Material (Reel 18)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 18)
    - Maps (Reel 18)
  - Leelanau County
    - Correspondence (Reel 18)
    - Historical Material (Reel 18)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 18)
    - Maps (Reel 18)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 18)
  - Lenawee County
    - Correspondence (Reel 18)
    - Historical Material (Reel 18)
    - Draft of Guide (Reel 18)
    - Maps (Reel 18)
  - Livingston County
    - Historical Material (Reel 18)
    - Maps (Reel 18)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings (Draft of Guide) (Reel 18)
  - Luce County
    - Historical Material (Reel 18)
    - Maps (Reel 18)
  - Mackinac County
    - Correspondence (Reel 19)
    - Historical Material (Reel 19)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 19)
    - Maps (Reel 19)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 19)
  - Macomb County
    - Historical Material (Reel 19)
    - Maps (Reel 19)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - County Clerk (Reel 19)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 19)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 19)
      - Friend of the Court (Reel 19)
      - Probate Court (Reel 19)
      - Concealed Weapon Licensing Board (Reel 19)
      - Coroner (Reel 19)
      - Treasurer (Reel 19)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 19)
      - Superintendents of the Poor (Reel 19)
      - Soldiers' Relief Commission (Reel 19)
      - Road Commission (Reel 19)
      - Drain Commissioner (Reel 19)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 19)
  - Manistee County
    - Historical Material (Reel 19)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 19)
    - Maps (Reel 19)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 19)
      - County Clerk (Reel 19)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 19)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 19)
      - Probate Court (Reel 19)
      - Sheriff (Reel 19)
      - Concealed Weapon Licensing Board (Reel 19)
      - Coroner (Reel 19)
      - Prosecuting Attorney (Reel 19)
      - Treasurer (Reel 19)
      - School Commission (Reel 19)
      - County Health Department (Reel 19)
      - Poor Commission (Reel 19)
      - Board of Election Commissioners (Reel 19)
      - Road Commission (Reel 19)
      - Drain Commission (Reel 19)
      - County Plat Board (Reel 19)
      - Agricultural Agent (Reel 19)
  - Marquette County
    - Correspondence (Reel 20)
    - Historical Material (Reel 20)
    - Maps (Reel 20)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records
      - County (Reel 20)
      - Townships
        - Champion (Reel 20)
        - Chocolay (Reel 20)
        - Ely (Reel 20)
        - Ewing (Reel 20)
        - Forsyth (Reel 20)
        - Humboldt (Reel 20)
        - Michigamme (Reel 20)
        - Negaunee (Reel 20)
        - Powell (Reel 20)
        - Sands (Reel 20)
        - Skandia (Reel 20)
        - Tilden (Reel 20)
        - Turin (Reel 20)
        - West Branch (Reel 20)
      - Municipalities
        - Marquette (Reel 20)
        - Ishpeming (Reel 20)
        - Negaunee (Reel 20)
  - Mason County
    - Correspondence (Reel 20)
    - Historical Material (Reel 20)
    - Draft of Guide-Government Organization (Reel 20)
    - Maps (Reel 20)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 20)
  - Mecosta County
    - Correspondence (Reel 20)
    - Historical Material (Reel 20)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 20)
    - Maps (Reel 20)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 20)
      - County Clerk (Reel 20)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 20)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 20)
      - Probate Court (Reel 21)
      - Sheriff (Reel 21)
      - Concealed Weapon Licensing Board (Reel 21)
      - Coroner (Reel 21)
      - Treasurer (Reel 21)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 21)
      - Board of School Examiners (Reel 21)
      - County Health Department (Reel 21)
      - Superintendents of the Poor (Reel 21)
      - Board of Election Commissioners (Reel 21)
      - Board of Canvassers (Reel 21)
      - Road Commission (Reel 21)
      - Drain Commission (Reel 21)
      - Surveyor (Reel 21)
      - Agricultural Agent (Reel 21)
  - Menominee County
    - Correspondence (Reel 21)
    - Draft of Guide-Historical (Reel 21)
    - Historical Material (Reel 21)
    - Draft of Guide-Government Organization (Reel 21)
    - Maps (Reel 21)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 21)
  - Midland County
    - Historical Material (Reel 21)
    - Maps (Reel 21)
  - Missaukee County
    - Correspondence (Reel 21)
    - Historical Material (Reel 21)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 22)
    - Maps (Reel 22)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 22)
  - Monroe County
    - Correspondence (Reel 22)
    - Historical Material (Reel 22)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 22)
    - Maps (Reel 22)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 22)
  - Montcalm County
    - Correspondence (Reel 22)
    - Historical Material (Reel 22)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 22)
    - Maps (Reel 22)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 22)
  - Montmorency County
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 22)
    - Maps (Reel 22)
  - Muskegon County
    - Correspondence (Reel 22)
    - Historical Material (Reel 22)
    - Maps (Reel 22)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 22)
  - Newaygo County
    - Maps (Reel 22)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 22)
      - County Clerk (Reel 22)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 22)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 22)
      - Probate Court (Reel 22)
      - Sheriff (Reel 22)
      - Concealed Weapon Licensing Board (Reel 22)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 22)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 22)
      - Board of School Examiners (Reel 22)
      - County Health Department (Reel 22)
      - Superintendents of the Poor (Reel 22)
      - Soldiers' Relief Commission (Reel 22)
      - Board of Canvassers (Reel 22)
      - Drain Commissioner (Reel 22)
      - Surveyor (Reel 22)
  - Oakland County
    - Correspondence (Reel 22)
    - Historical Material (Reel 22)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 22)
    - Maps (Reel 22)
  - Oceana County
    - Maps (Reel 23)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 23)
      - County Clerk (Reel 23)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 23)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 23)
      - Probate Court (Reel 23)
      - Coroner (Reel 23)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 23)
      - Board of Election Commissioners (Reel 23)
  - Ogemaw County
    - Historical Material (Reel 23)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 23)
    - Maps (Reel 23)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 23)
  - Ontonagon County
    - Historical Material (Reel 23)
    - Maps (Reel 23)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 23)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 23)
      - County Clerk (Reel 23)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 23)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 23)
      - Probate Court (Reel 23)
      - Concealed Weapon Licensing Board (Reel 23)
      - Coroner (Reel 23)
      - Prosecuting Attorney (Reel 23)
      - Treasurer (Reel 23)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 23)
      - Superintendent of the Poor (Reel 23)
      - Board of Canvassers (Reel 23)
      - Road Commission (Reel 23)
      - Drain Commissioner (Reel 23)
      - Surveyor (Reel 23)
  - Osceola County
    - Correspondence (Reel 23)
    - Historical Material (Reel 23)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 23)
    - Maps (Reel 23)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 23)
  - Oscoda County
    - Historical Material (Reel 24)
    - Maps (Reel 24)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 24)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 24)
      - County Clerk (Reel 24)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 24)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 24)
      - Circuit Court Commissioners (Reel 24)
      - Concealed Weapon Licensing board (Reel 24)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 24)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 24)
      - Board of Election Commissioners (Reel 24)
      - Board of Canvassers (Reel 24)
      - Road Commission (Reel 24)
  - Otsego County
    - Correspondence (Reel 24)
    - Historical Material (Reel 24)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 24)
    - Maps (Reel 24)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 24)
      - County Clerk (Reel 24)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 24)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 24)
      - Probate Court (Reel 24)
      - Sheriff (Reel 24)
      - Concealed Weapon Licensing Board (Reel 24)
      - Coroner (Reel 24)
      - Prosecuting Attorney (Reel 24)
      - Tax Allocation Board (Reel 24)
      - Treasurer (Reel 24)
      - Sinking Fund (Reel 24)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 24)
      - Board of School Examiners (Reel 24)
      - Department of Social Welfare (Reel 24)
      - Board of Canvassers (Reel 24)
      - Road Commission (Reel 24)
      - Agricultural Agent (Reel 24)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 24)
  - Ottawa County
    - Historical Material (Reel 24)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 24)
    - Maps (Reel 24)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 24)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - County Treasurer (Reel 24)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 24)
  - Presque Isle County
    - Historical Material (Reel 25)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 25)
    - Maps (Reel 25)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 25)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 25)
      - County Clerk (Reel 25)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 25)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 25)
      - Probate Court (Reel 25)
      - Sheriff (Reel 25)
      - Coroner (Reel 25)
      - Treasurer (Reel 25)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 25)
      - Superintendent of the Poor (Reel 25)
      - Road Commission (Reel 25)
  - Roscommon County
    - Correspondence (Reel 25)
    - Historical Material (Reel 25)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 25)
    - Maps (Reel 25)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - County Clerk (Reel 25)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 25)
      - Probate Court (Reel 25)
      - Sheriff (Reel 25)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 25)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 25)
      - Road Commission (Reel 25)
  - Saginaw County
    - Correspondence (Reel 25)
    - Draft of Guide-Historical (Reel 25)
    - Historical Material (Reel 25)
    - Historical Material (cont.) (Reel 26)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 26)
    - Maps (Reel 26)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 26)
    - Inventory of Maps (Reel 26)
  - St. Clair County
    - Historical Material (Reel 26)
    - Maps (Reel 26)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 26)
      - County Clerk (Reel 26)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 26)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 26)
      - Probate Court (Reel 26)
      - Probation Officer (Reel 26)
      - Sheriff (Reel 26)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 26)
      - Superintendent of the Poor (Reel 26)
      - Board of Election Commissioners (Reel 26)
      - Drain Commissioner (Reel 26)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 26)
  - St. Joseph County
    - Historical Material (Reel 26)
    - Maps (Reel 26)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 26)
  - Sanilac County
    - Correspondence (Reel 27)
    - Historical Material (Reel 27)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 27)
    - Maps (Reel 27)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 27)
  - Schoolcraft County
    - Historical Material (Reel 27)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 27)
    - Maps (Reel 27)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 27)
      - County Clerk (Reel 27)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 27)
      - Probate Court (Reel 27)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 27)
      - School Commission (Reel 27)
      - County Health Department (Reel 27)
      - Superintendent of the Poor (Reel 27)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 27)
  - Shiawassee County
    - Draft of Guide (Reel 27)
    - Historical Material (Reel 27)
    - Maps (Reel 27)
  - Tuscola County
    - Correspondence (Reel 27)
    - Historical Material (Reel 27)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 28)
    - Maps (Reel 28)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 28)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 28)
      - County Clerk (Reel 28)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 28)
      - Probate Court (Reel 28)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 28)
  - Van Buren County
    - Correspondence (Reel 28)
    - Historical Material (Reel 28)
    - Maps (Reel 28)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 28)
      - County Clerk (Reel 28)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 28)
      - Probate Court (Reel 28)
      - Tax Allocation Board (Reel 28)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 28)
      - School Commissioner (Reel 28)
      - Superintendent of the Poor (Reel 28)
      - Road Commission (Reel 28)
      - Drain Commissioner (Reel 28)
      - Agricultural Agent (Reel 28)
    - Inventory of Maps in County (Reel 28)
  - Washtenaw County
    - Correspondence (Reel 28)
    - Historical Material (Reel 28)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 28)
    - Maps (Reel 28)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 28)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - County Clerk (Reel 28)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 28)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 28)
      - Sheriff (Reel 28)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 28)
      - Poor Commission (Reel 28)
      - Road Commission (Reel 28)
  - Wayne County
    - Correspondence (Reel 28)
    - Historical Material (Reel 28)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 28)
    - Maps (Reel 28)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 28)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 28)
      - County Clerk (Reel 28)
      - County Clerk (cont.) (Reel 29)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 29)
      - Abstract Department (Reel 29)
      - Circuit Court (including Old Territorial Court, Old County Court, Old Superior Court of Detroit, Old Justice Court, and Common Pleas Court) (Reel 29)
      - Circuit Court Commissioners (Reel 29)
      - Friend of the Court (Reel 29)
      - Jury Commission (Reel 29)
      - Probate Court (Reel 29)
      - Sheriff (Reel 29)
      - Coroner (Reel 29)
      - Prosecuting Attorney (Reel 29)
      - Bureau of Taxation (Reel 29)
      - Tax Allocation Board (Reel 29)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 29)
      - County Auditors (Reel 29)
      - County Auditors (cont.) (Reel 30)
      - Controllers (Reel 30)
      - Sinking Fund Commission (Reel 30)
      - Superintendent of Schools (Reel 30)
      - Superintendents of the Poor (Reel 30)
      - Social Welfare Department-County Agent (Reel 30)
      - Wayne County Training School (Reel 30)
      - Soldiers' Relief Commission (Reel 30)
      - Board of Election Commissioners (Reel 30)
      - Board of Canvassers (Reel 30)
      - Road Commission (Reel 30)
      - Port of Detroit Authority (Reel 30)
      - Drain Commissioner (Reel 30)
      - Surveyor (Reel 30)
      - Library Commission (Reel 30)
      - Agricultural Agent (Reel 30)
  - Wexford County
    - Correspondence (Reel 31)
    - Historical Material (Reel 31)
    - Maps (Reel 31)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Supervisors (Reel 31)
      - County Clerk (Reel 31)
      - Register of Deeds (Reel 31)
      - Circuit Court (Reel 31)
      - Sheriff (Reel 31)
      - Concealed Weapons Licensing board (Reel 31)
      - Prosecuting Attorney (Reel 31)
      - County Treasurer (Reel 31)
      - School Commission (Reel 31)
      - Superintendents of the Poor (Reel 31)
      - Road Commission (Reel 31)
      - Drain Commissioner (Reel 31)
- Survey of Municipal Records
  The Survey of municipal Records (a little over six linear feet of material) covers the same types of information as that of the counties, with the exception of maps; there were no special maps drawn and none inventoried. The offices of county government have their counterparts at the municipal level, with some differences. Those offices for which inventories are available include: Mayor, City Manager, Common Council, City Clerk, Recorder, Recorder's Court, Justices of the Peace, City/Municipal Court, Common Pleas Court, Probate Court, Treasurer, Comptroller/Controller, Sinking Fund Commission, Corporation Counsel, Police Department, Fire Department, Department/Board of Public Works, Water Department, Department of Building Safety and Engineering, Plumbing Inspector, Electric Light Inspector, Public Lighting Commission, City Assessors/Board of Assessors, Auditor General, Board of Health/Health Department, City Attorney, Board of Education, City Surveyor, Public Library, Sealer of Weights and Measures, Department of Parks and Recreation/Board of Park Commissioners/Department of Parks and Boulevards, Street Department/Superintendent of Streets, Department of Street Railways, City Engineer, Purchasing Agent/Department, Planning Commission, Election Commission, Welfare Department, Civil Service Commission, City Chemist, Ways and Means Commission, Board of Review, Board of Estimates, and Bridge Commission. The original order of these records has been retained, except for some relating to Detroit. Forms for old records of the Detroit City Clerk's Office, Controller's Office, Treasurer's Office, Common Council, and Department of Public Works were filed by H.R.S. workers under "Municipal Garage", where they had been stored and subsequently inventoried. Many of the records were later sent to the Detroit Public Library or destroyed. Their inventory forms have now been filed according to the departments which created them.
  Only a few municipalities were researched as separate entities, beyond the "chief city" requirements for the county files: Alpena, Battle Creek, Bay City, Charlotte, Cheboygan, Detroit, Escanaba, Grand Rapids, Hamtramck, Jackson, Kalamazoo, Marquette, Menominee, Muskegon, and Port Huron. The criteria for saving or discarding materials were the same as for the county files. Researchers interested in a particular city should check the county files as well as these. They should also consult the transcripts of municipal records, which include council proceedings, local ordinances, and some other types of records (see contents list).
  - Alpena
    - Correspondence (Reel 31)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 31)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Common Council (Reel 31)
      - City Clerk (Reel 31)
      - Justice of the Peace (Reel 31)
      - Police Department (Reel 31)
      - City Treasurer (Reel 31)
      - Board of Education (Reel 31)
      - Health Department (Reel 31)
      - Water Department (Reel 31)
  - Battle Creek
    - Correspondence (Reel 31)
    - Historical Material (Reel 31)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 31)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 31)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Recorder (Reel 31)
      - Municipal Court (Reel 31)
      - Sealer of Weights and Measures (Reel 31)
      - Treasurer (Reel 31)
      - City Assessor (Reel 31)
      - Comptroller (Reel 31)
      - Fire Department (Reel 31)
      - Health Department (Reel 31)
      - Department of Public Works (Reel 31)
  - Bay City
    - Historical Material (Reel 31)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 32)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Mayor (Reel 32)
      - City Manager (Reel 32)
      - City Clerk (Reel 32)
      - City Recorder (Reel 32)
      - Recorder's Court (Reel 32)
      - Treasurer (Reel 32)
      - Comptroller (Reel 32)
      - Police Department (Reel 32)
      - Fire Department (Reel 32)
      - Board of Public Works (Reel 32)
      - City Assessors (Reel 32)
      - Board of Health (Reel 32)
      - Water Department (Reel 32)
      - Plumbing Inspector (Reel 32)
      - Electric Light Department (Reel 33)
      - City Attorney (Reel 33)
      - Board of Education (Reel 33)
      - City Surveyor (Reel 33)
      - Board of Park Commissioners (Reel 33)
      - Street Department (Reel 33)
      - Purchasing Department (Reel 33)
      - City Engineer (Reel 33)
      - City Chemist (Reel 33)
      - Board of Review (Reel 33)
      - Ways and Means Committee (Reel 33)
      - Board of Estimates (Reel 33)
      - Bridge Commission (Reel 33)
  - Charlotte
    - Correspondence (Reel 33)
    - Historical Material (Reel 33)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 33)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - City Clerk (Reel 33)
  - Cheboygan
    - Historical Material (Reel 33)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 33)
  - Detroit
    - Correspondence (Reel 33)
    - Historical Material (Reel 33)
    - Historical Material-Government Organization (Reel 33)
    - Historical-Govt. Org.-Department of Public Welfare (Reel 34)
    - Housing, Care, and Accessibility of Records (Reel 34)
    - Inventory of Government Department Holdings
      - Board of Assessors (Reel 34)
      - Auditor General (Reel 34)
      - Dept. of Building Safety and Engineering (Reel 34)
      - City Clerk (Reel 34)
      - Civil Service Commission (Reel 35)